

Contact



Phone +54 9 1132418964



Email

emanuel. rodriguez. bedeman @gmail.com



Address

Lanús Oeste, Argentina



Linkedin

in/emanuel-rodriguez-bedeman/



Github /EmanuelRodriguezBedeman

Education

2022 - 2023 **Web Development**Self Taught

2021 - Ongoing

Python, SQL & Dashboards
Self Taught

2014 - 2023

Medicine

Universidad de Buenos Aires (UBA)

Expertise

- Python & SQL Development
- Data Analysis & Science
- Web Development

Language

English

Upper Intermediate

Emanuel Rodriguez Bedeman

Professional Profile

Medical student and programmer with experience in both areas and specialized in data. With knowledge not only in healthcare related data, but also in business data. Determined, very inquisitive in many fields and technologies, very empathetic and always open to share knowledge and create new solutions that can improve people's life through accessibility options.

Experience

O 2022 - Ongoing

Laboratorio de innovación en tecnología y salúd pública | Argentina

Data Analyst

- Study the performance of UBA's medical students through the analysis of different academic aspects and Databases, with the goal of creating a model that predicts the chances of student desertion.
- Analyze data patterns to create features which in turn provide new insight to understanding student behavior, increasing efficiency in the models and the predictions that can be made with them.
- Improve workflow and communication via Google Colab and Slack.
- Use of data technologies which includes Python, Pandas and Numpy.
- Use of visualization technologies which includes the use Matplotlib and Seaborn.
- Use of modeling technologies which includes Scikit-Learn and Catboost.

0 2022 - 2023

Developer | Buenos Aires, Argentina.

Web developer

- Developing projects for my portfolio, to broaden my capabilities and learn new technologies along the journey.
- Determined to learn new tools with different gradients of complexity that ensure efficient solutions and comfort to the client as well as new accessibility options.
- Use of frontend frameworks such as Bootstrap, and Tailwind.

Projects

Project CRUD

Python & SQLite

Very simple desktop app that quickly creates a SQLite databases with static fields, connect to any of them and make simple CRUD operations. It also includes a very small tutorial for the client, explaining how to properly use it without the need of any technical experience.

It is tested to be errors proof, so the client can use it without the risk of breaking it, also has warning signs before taking any decision that can lead to this.

The objective (o goal) is to supply a potential client with a software for their small/big business and create a database for it, for them to use it to control the products displayed in an e-commerce without the need of a developer always beside them.

Dengue Dashboard

Looker Studio

Developed a dashboard to monitor the epidemiological situation of Dengue in the City of Buenos Aires, Argentina. This involved tracking the count of patients requiring medical hospitalization, those admitted to the intensive care unit, and the mortality rate. The analysis also included a detailed breakdown based on administrative districts (comunas) and age groups.